Zerina Getriani

nohp | email | domisili

Fresh graduate jurusan student from kampus with ipk GPA. organization experience. Good at public speaking, several times invited as speaker in college events. Have excellent communication skills, time management, critical thinking and multitasking. Fast learner and love to learn new things.

Profile	
Place of Birth :	
Date of Birth :	
Gender :	
Nationality :	
Education	
IPB University	2019-2023
 Major in 	
• Current GPA	
Research Experience	
Thesis (optional)	2022-2023
 Penjelasan singkat mengenai skripsi 	
Organization Experience	
Nama Organisasi	2021-2022
 Posisi 	
Nama Organisasi	2021-2022
 Posisi 	
Nama Organisasi	2021-2022
 Posisi 	
Leadership Experience	
Nama Organisasi	2021-2022
Penjelasan jobdesk sebagai ketua	
Nama Organisasi	2021-2022
 Penjelasan jobdesk sebagai ketua 	
Nama Organisasi	2021-2022

• Penjelasan jobdesk sebagai ketua

Internship Experience

Nama Perusahaan	2022
 Posisi 	
Penjelasan posisi	
Nama Perusahaan	2022
 Posisi 	
Penjelasan posisi	
Committee Experience	
Nama Kepanitiaan	2020
 Posisi 	
Nama Kepanitiaan	2020
 Posisi 	
Nama Kepanitiaan	2020
 Posisi 	
Laboratory Assistant Experience (kalau ada)	
Laboratory Assistant	2021
The state of the s	

• Penjelasan pekerjaan